{
    "entityName": "28170300402-MPPS PULIPADU_SC",
    "observationName": "School safety checklist -Officials",
    "observationId": "5f990e16be0e60389529e33a",
    "entityType": "school",
    "entityId": "5e6b4ffd135b2d734252d21f",
    "districtName": "GUNTUR",
    "response": [{
        "order": "462A01",
        "question": "Let's start capturing your observation notes",
        "responseType": "matrix",
        "answers": [],
        "chart": {},
        "instanceQuestions": [{
            "order": "462A02",
            "question": "Name",
            "responseType": "text",
            "answers": ["test"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A03",
            "question": "Designation",
            "responseType": "text",
            "answers": ["abc"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A04",
            "question": "Date of visit",
            "responseType": "date",
            "answers": ["21 Dec 2020, 9:14:16 AM"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A05",
            "question": "School ID",
            "responseType": "number",
            "answers": ["2"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A06",
            "question": "Zone",
            "responseType": "text",
            "answers": ["test"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A07",
            "question": "HoS Name",
            "responseType": "text",
            "answers": ["test"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A08",
            "question": "HoS contact number",
            "responseType": "number",
            "answers": ["2"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A09",
            "question": "Are there any open drains, potholes/ pits inside or outside the school?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Yes"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Yes",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A10",
            "question": "Can the entrance to school be monitored from the principal’s office?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A11",
            "question": "Can visitors walk in directly into the school without supervision?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Partially"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Partially",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A12",
            "question": "Are important phone numbers displayed?",
            "responseType": "multiselect",
            "answers": [
                ["Child Line"]
            ],
            "chart": {
                "type": "bar",
                "data": [{
                    "data": [100]
                }],
                "xAxis": {
                    "categories": ["Child Line"],
                    "title": {
                        "text": "Responses"
                    }
                },
                "yAxis": {
                    "min": 0,
                    "max": 100,
                    "title": {
                        "text": "Responses in percentage"
                    }
                }
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A13",
            "question": "Are nursery classes (if applicable) situated on the ground floor?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A14",
            "question": "Is the drinking water area clean?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A15",
            "question": "Does the school have filtered drinking water facility?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Partially"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Partially",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A16",
            "question": "Is the water tank clean? Ensure it does not  have mud, algae , dead insects.",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A17",
            "question": "Are the toilets clean overall?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A18",
            "question": "Is there a soap/ hand-wash in the toilet?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Partially"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Partially",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A19",
            "question": "Is there running water supply in the toilet?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Partially"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Partially",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A20",
            "question": "Are the cisterns/flush functional?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Partially"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Partially",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A21",
            "question": "Is the first-aid box fully equipped? (Check expiry date)",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A22",
            "question": "Does the school have a designated vehicle for emergency situations?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Partially"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Partially",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A23",
            "question": "Are the corners of corridors and walls clean?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A24",
            "question": "Are there abandoned objects lying in any corner of the school?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Partially"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Partially",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A25",
            "question": "Does the MCD pick up garbage from school everyday?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A26",
            "question": "Do you see students fighting or misbehaving during lunch break?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["No"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "No",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A27",
            "question": "What do teachers do when such things happen?",
            "responseType": "multiselect",
            "answers": [
                ["Talk to students fighting"]
            ],
            "chart": {
                "type": "bar",
                "data": [{
                    "data": [100]
                }],
                "xAxis": {
                    "categories": ["Talk to students fighting"],
                    "title": {
                        "text": "Responses"
                    }
                },
                "yAxis": {
                    "min": 0,
                    "max": 100,
                    "title": {
                        "text": "Responses in percentage"
                    }
                }
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A28",
            "question": "Do some students bully others in school?",
            "responseType": "radio",
            "answers": ["Partially"],
            "chart": {
                "type": "pie",
                "plotOptions": {
                    "pie": {
                        "allowPointSelect": true,
                        "cursor": "pointer",
                        "dataLabels": {
                            "enabled": false
                        },
                        "showInLegend": true
                    }
                },
                "data": [{
                    "data": [{
                        "name": "Partially",
                        "y": 100
                    }]
                }]
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A29",
            "question": "What kinds of punishments are given to children who misbehave / don’t do homework etc?",
            "responseType": "multiselect",
            "answers": [
                ["Standing inside/outside class"]
            ],
            "chart": {
                "type": "bar",
                "data": [{
                    "data": [100]
                }],
                "xAxis": {
                    "categories": ["Standing inside/outside class"],
                    "title": {
                        "text": "Responses"
                    }
                },
                "yAxis": {
                    "min": 0,
                    "max": 100,
                    "title": {
                        "text": "Responses in percentage"
                    }
                }
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A30",
            "question": "What happens when a child is hurt?",
            "responseType": "multiselect",
            "answers": [
                ["Sent home/parents called"]
            ],
            "chart": {
                "type": "bar",
                "data": [{
                    "data": [100]
                }],
                "xAxis": {
                    "categories": ["Sent home/parents called"],
                    "title": {
                        "text": "Responses"
                    }
                },
                "yAxis": {
                    "min": 0,
                    "max": 100,
                    "title": {
                        "text": "Responses in percentage"
                    }
                }
            },
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A31",
            "question": "Call 5 students of class 3/4/5 (randomly). Ask them to read a text from their Hindi books and record the count of students who could read it.",
            "responseType": "number",
            "answers": ["2"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }, {
            "order": "462A32",
            "question": "Please record your overall comments on the state of the following in the school: \n1. Corporal punishment \n2. Bullying \n3. Reading level in school",
            "responseType": "text",
            "answers": ["T"],
            "chart": {},
            "instanceQuestions": []
        }]
    }],
    "allQuestions": [{
        "questionName": "Name",
        "questionExternalId": "462A02",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d922"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Designation",
        "questionExternalId": "462A03",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d923"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Date of visit",
        "questionExternalId": "462A04",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d924"
    }, {
        "questionName": "School ID",
        "questionExternalId": "462A05",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d925"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Zone",
        "questionExternalId": "462A06",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d926"
    }, {
        "questionName": "HoS Name",
        "questionExternalId": "462A07",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d927"
    }, {
        "questionName": "HoS contact number",
        "questionExternalId": "462A08",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d928"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Are there any open drains, potholes/ pits inside or outside the school?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A09",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d929"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Can the entrance to school be monitored from the principal’s office?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A10",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d92a"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Can visitors walk in directly into the school without supervision?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A11",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d92b"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Are important phone numbers displayed?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A12",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d92c"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Are nursery classes (if applicable) situated on the ground floor?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A13",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d92d"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Is the drinking water area clean?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A14",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d92e"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Does the school have filtered drinking water facility?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A15",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d92f"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Is the water tank clean? Ensure it does not  have mud, algae , dead insects.",
        "questionExternalId": "462A16",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d930"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Are the toilets clean overall?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A17",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d931"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Is there a soap/ hand-wash in the toilet?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A18",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d932"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Is there running water supply in the toilet?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A19",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d933"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Are the cisterns/flush functional?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A20",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d934"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Is the first-aid box fully equipped? (Check expiry date)",
        "questionExternalId": "462A21",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d935"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Does the school have a designated vehicle for emergency situations?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A22",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d936"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Are the corners of corridors and walls clean?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A23",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d937"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Are there abandoned objects lying in any corner of the school?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A24",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d938"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Does the MCD pick up garbage from school everyday?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A25",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d939"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Do you see students fighting or misbehaving during lunch break?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A26",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d93a"
    }, {
        "questionName": "What do teachers do when such things happen?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A27",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d93b"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Do some students bully others in school?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A28",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d93c"
    }, {
        "questionName": "What kinds of punishments are given to children who misbehave / don’t do homework etc?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A29",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d93d"
    }, {
        "questionName": "What happens when a child is hurt?",
        "questionExternalId": "462A30",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d93e"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Call 5 students of class 3/4/5 (randomly). Ask them to read a text from their Hindi books and record the count of students who could read it.",
        "questionExternalId": "462A31",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d93f"
    }, {
        "questionName": "Please record your overall comments on the state of the following in the school: \n1. Corporal punishment \n2. Bullying \n3. Reading level in school",
        "questionExternalId": "462A32",
        "questionId": "5d70f9af7afa105d7d66d940"
    }]
}